Hey.
This is no place to be right now.
So fly away.
You've got wings. Use them.
Falco!
Brother? Why are you here?
Good. I'm glad you're
able to talk at least.
Colt, move!
I'll carry you back.
Try to hold on!
Falco!
Report. What happened, Colt?
The Eldian advance squad
has been wiped out.
They took a direct hit
from an artillery shell
and got blown to bits.
What of the trench?
It's hopeless.
We can't dig any further!
Oh? And who decided that?
Are you trying to give
me orders now, Eldian?
Insubordinate mutt!
You watch your tone
with Commander Magath!
But, sir. If things
keep going like this...
Falco. You look like
you're drunk.
Guess he must've hit
his head pretty good.
How much of the last four years
do you remember, Falco?
You know we're at war, right?
Who are you people?
Where am I?
I don't get it.
Wasn't I just flying around with
a couple of swords in my hands?
Whoo. Like that.
And there were Titans, too...
Okay. It sounds like
we're gonna have to
re-explain the entire operation.
Just do your best to keep up, Falco.
Here goes:
This war's dragged on for four years now,
but with this battle, we can end it.
All we have to do is capture Fort Slava.
Well, to be exact, we have to destroy
the Mid-East Allied Forces'
fleet in the harbor beneath it.
Once those ships are sunk,
we'll have won this war for Marley.
But Fort Slava defends the high
ground overlooking the harbor,
which means there's
no attacking that fleet
from land without control of the fort.
So why can't the Marleyan fleet just
attack them from the sea?
Come on, Zofia!
Do you really think we can count
on that navy to do a thing?
It took them four
whole years to establish
any vestige of control over the seas!
And this shouldn't really be a surprise,
but they lost half their damn
battleships in the process!
So of course they're
too chickenshit to do
a single friggin' thing
until we've taken this
massive death trap of a fort for them!
Screw every single one of those
stupid, incompetent cowards!
Udo. Calm it down before
you squeeze Falco's head off.
Oh, uh. Sorry.
So what gives?
Why did they send us to the front lines?
It's not like four warrior candidates
can make a real difference.
First of all, you can speak for yourself.
Second, they wanna judge us.
They're choosing their next warrior.
The time is almost here.
Commander Magath chose the front lines
for the location of our final test.
He knows what's on the horizon.
The person he chooses
will be at the center
of the plan to conquer Paradis.
The successor to the Armored Titan.
The Armored Titan.
I wonder which one of us it'll be.
Shut up. No you don't.
You've made it perfectly
clear that you don't think
any of us come close to you, Gabi.
Well yeah, that's because you don't.
True. Gabi has us
three soundly beat.
Tch. Not in terms
of grades, she doesn't.
No. They don't care
about our grades, Udo.
It's like I keep telling you.
The difference between
me and the three of you
is that I'm prepared.
To shoulder the fate of us Eldians,
and purge that island of devils
who've only made us suffer.
I'll slaughter every one of them.
I'll win that war, and prove to the world
they don't have to fear us anymore.
That the only Eldians
left are good Eldians!
I won't be defeated.
Not until everyone in the
internment zone is set free.
Hey. Just what are
you doing with those?
Looks cool. Right?
It won't work, Commander Magath!
If we try to take out the railway tracks
with nothing but infantry,
we'll get mowed down
by machine-gun fire
before we can do a thing.
That trench is fully manned.
It's an airtight defense.
On top of that, they have artillery
supporting them from inside the fort.
If we stay put,
it's only a matter of time
before shells start
raining down on our heads.
It sounds like you
have an idea. Go on.
Let's use them.
We need to unleash Jaws and Cart now.
Galliard and Pieck
should be able to do it.
They can wipe out
the enemies in the trench
and the pillbox in the blink of an eye.
Won't work.
They'll beat us if we're playing
our cards the wrong way.
Commander Magath.
It's coming through now.
What is, sir?
A train. An armored train.
Equipped with two big guns in the front,
and two more in the back.
They're the Allied Forces'
newest weapons:
Anti-Titan cannons.
They fire 150-millimeter
armor piercing shells,
capable of bringing down
a Titan with a single shot.
Even one of the Nine.
Maybe, but both of our Titans
are incredibly fast, sir.
The odds of them getting
hit in the neck are so...
And, what if it happens?
We'd lose a warrior, and the
power of yet another Titan.
Plus there's no guarantee
that we'd be able to reclaim that power.
That's right. We'd be
repeating the mistake we made
when we tried to take the
Founding Titan nine years ago.
We're two Titans down.
We need to protect the ones we have left.
The loss of the Colossal
and Female Titans
caused a perceived lapse
in Marley's strength.
That sparked this war and
delayed the Paradis Operation.
What is it that makes our motherland
the great empire it is today?
The Nine, sir. Or the seven.
Five now.
And our nation won't last if
we keep throwing them away.
The power of Marley's Titans is absolute,
that is a fact which must never change.
Line up the Eldians.
Have them prepare for a charge.
Yes, sir!
Please reconsider!
If they charge...
What's the matter, Eldian?
Are you not loyal soldiers who've sworn
to fight and die for Marley?
This is a chance for the 800 Eldians here
to atone for the past and serve
our motherland with honor.
Yes. All creatures drink
of joy at nature's breast.
All Right.
Soldiers at the ready!
Up! Prepare to attack!
Come on! Stand up!
Eldians! Your target is
the enemy railway track.
It's well defended, but you
must succeed at any cost.
Guard the suicide squad.
They'll charge the enemy bunker
and disable their machine gun.
You may be spawn of the devil,
but through your actions here,
you can cleanse yourselves
of that disgrace!
This is your chance to honor
and be honored in turn
by our motherland!
Prepare to prove your worth.
Yes, sir!
You Warrior candidates
will stand by here.
If I have to trade 800 Eldian soldiers
to take out those tracks, then so be it,
but the tracks must be destroyed.
As long as that armored train is
prowling the fort's perimeter,
neither Beast nor Armored
can be called upon
to finish the job.
Yeah. I know, but...
Look, Colt.
You're the chosen successor
of the Beast Titan.
You need to take a page from Zeke's book
and learn what it means to lead.
Perfect. We can destroy
the tracks and the train.
Why don't'cha let me handle this, sir?
Huh?
Ta-da! If you'll let me.
I'm sure that I can take out
that armored train by myself!
Hey. Wait.
You're too valuable an asset.
This country spent a lot of
money to train you. Denied.
It's true. I'm super valuable,
especially compared to these three.
Honestly, you might never
find a warrior candidate
who's as talented as me.
Even then. They won't
be this cute.
But if I pull this off,
you can take out the train
without needing to sacrifice
that 800-man unit!
And if you fail?
Then you'll lose your
most promising candidate,
as well as a bundle of
seven hand grenades.
That said, sir, if you really
think I'm more valuable
than 800 Eldian infantrymen, I get it.
To think that you'd sacrifice
that many soldiers just for me.
I knew you loved me deep down,
but I didn't know how deep.
Fine. Go ahead.
No. Gabi.
Mark my words.
I'll destroy that train and
prove no warrior candidate
deserves to inherit
the Armor more than me.
What are you doing?
My plan won't work
if I'm in uniform, sir.
With your permission, I'd like
to remove my armband as well.
Granted.
Hey. There's someone
coming. Look there.
It's a woman. A girl, really.
Looks like she's trying to surrender.
Yeah, right. Don't trust it,
she could be Eldian.
She's limping, as if she's
wounded or something.
Maybe her foot's been shackled?
Who
cares? She probably is Eldian.
Shoot her before she transforms!
I don't shoot kids.
You've got a gun:
If you wanna shoot her, do it.
Shit.
What the...?
Not yet.
Wait for it.
She's just lying there.
Who cares? Shoot her!
Here goes nothing!
She pulled it off.
Galliard! You're up!
Dammit! You cowardly bastards.
This... is exactly why
we should kill every one of you on sight.
Gabi!
Hold on. Falco!
Galliard, thank you!
Our forces have disabled
the armored train.
We can now commence the airborne assault.
The plan from this point
is straightforward.
Zeke will be our spear,
and Reiner our shield.
That really hurts, damn it.
I'm a Marleyan, so why...
'Kay.
Hey, what are you doing? Falco?
Come on. You know.
This guy's done.
He's in no shape to fight anymore.
Udo. Can you spare a tourniquet?
Dumb brat. You should've
just finished him off.
Is this supposed to be your
big selling point, Falco?
You wanna outshine the girl who
just won this battle for Marley
by being a stickler for the laws of war?
This won't help you earn the Armored.
I don't care.
You're such a weirdo.
He's saying something.
Can you interpret?
Tell him that I managed
to stop his bleeding
so he doesn't need to be afra...
"Do not touch me."
"I'll be tainted."
"You filthy devil," he says.
Retreat!
Hurry up!
Get away from the fort!
Don't get caught in it!
It's beginning.
No! Please!
It's true.
You people are devils.
The Marleyans I'm descended from
were preyed upon in the same way.
By Eldians like you.
Fire!
The kinetic bombardment was effective,
but due to the height
they were dropped from,
roughly half the Titans deployed
were killed on impact.
The enemy still has a number
of anti-Titan cannons.
That's 28.29.
I know how many and where they are now.
But still.
Another wall.
I'm sick and tired
of all these walls.
It's the Armored!
Hurry and kill it!
Fire!
The new Anti-Titan shells...
They can even pierce my armor.
What the...? What hit me?
An armored train.
There's another?
Shit!
Fi...
Galliard!
Sons of the devil's whore!
It's done.
So the fort's been cleared.
It's our failure that allowed
this war to happen, Reiner.
But every war is awful, don't you agree?
After four long years,
we're about to win the war.
Following the loss of their fleet,
the Mid-East Allied Forces had no choice
but to sign a peace treaty
on Marley's terms.
It was a long, difficult war for Marley,
but it did end in victory.
However, the war also made it
clear to the whole world
that the power of Titans
would soon be eclipsed.
Knowing this, the leaders of
Marley would resolve to obtain
the Founding Titan
as quickly as possible.
Oh no.
Thanks to the incomparable
bravery of the Marleyan army,
Fort Slava fell and the
Mid-East fleet was sunk!
Yeah! That's incredible!
I knew our soldiers would pull it off!
Titan strength is not absolute.
Marley was shown this painful reality.
Having secured a moment
of peace through their victory,
the Eldians return to
their hometown of Liberio.
Next episode: "Midnight Train."